<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GatePreviousYear</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="Question1_2019_set1">A certain processor uses a fully associative cache of size 16 kB, The cache block size is 16 bytes. Assume that the main memory is byte addressable and uses a 32-bit address. How many bits are required for the Tag and the Index fields respectively in the addresses generated by the processor?</string>
    <string name="option1_question1_2019_set1">28 bits and 0 bits</string>
    <string name="option2_question1_2019_set1">24 bits and 0 bit</string>
    <string name="option3_question1_2019_set1">28 bits and 4 bits</string>
    <string name="option4_question1_2019_set1">24 bits and 4 bits</string>
    <string name="Question2_2019_set1"><![CDATA[Let G be an undirected complete graph on n vertices, where n > 2. Then, the number of different Hamiltonian cycles in G is equal to]]></string>
    <string name="Question3_2019_set1"><![CDATA[Consider a sequence of 14 elements: A = [-5, -10, 6, 3, -1, -2, 13, 4, -9, -1, 4, 12, -3, 0]. The subsequence sum . Determine the maximum of S(i,j), where 0 ≤ i ≤ j < 14.]]></string>
    <string name="Question4_2019_set1">The value of 3^51 mod is ________</string>
    <string name="Question5_2019_set1">Let U = {1, 2, …,n} and A = {(x, X)∣ x∈X, X⊆U }. Consider the following two statements on ∣A∣. Which of the above statements is/are TRUE?</string>
    <string name="Question6_2019_set1">Consider Z = X − Y where X, Y and Z are all in sign-magnitude form. X and Y are each represented in n bits. To avoid overflow, the representation of Z would require a minimum of:</string>
    <string name="Question8_2019_set1">Let G be an arbitrary group. Consider the following relations on G: R1: ∀a, b ∈ G, aR1b if and only if ∃g ∈ G such that a = g−1bg R2: ∀a, b ∈ G, aR2b if and only if a = b−1 Which of the above is/are equivalence relation/relations?</string>
    <string name="Question9_2019_set1"><![CDATA[Consider the following given grammar: \n S -> Aa \n A ->BD \n B-> b|ε \n D -> d|ε \n Let a , b ,d and $ be indexed as follows \n \ta\tb\td\t$\n\t3\t2\t1\t0 Compute the FOLLOW set of the non-terminal B and write the index values for the symbols in the FOLLOW set in the descending order. (For example, if the FOLLOW set is {a, b, d, $}, then the answer should be 3210)]]></string>
    <string name="Question10_2019_set1">For Σ = {a, b}, let us consider the regular language \n L = {x ∣ x = a2 + 3k or x = b10 + 12k, k ≥ 0} \n Which one of the following can be a pumping length (the constant guaranteed by the pumping lemma) for L?</string>
    <string name="Question11_2019_set1">If 𝐿 is a regular language over Σ = {𝑎,}, which one of the following languages is NOT regular?</string>
    <string name="Question14_2019_set1">The chip select logic for a certain DRAM chip in a memory system design is shown below. Assume that the memory system has 16 address lines denoted by A15 to A0. What is the range of addresses (in hexadecimal) of the memory system that can get enabled by the chip select (CS) signal?</string>
    <string name="Question15_2019_set1"><![CDATA[consider the following C program : \n #include <stdio.h> int r(){ static int num=7; return num--; } int main(){ for (r();r();r()) printf(“%d”,r()); return 0; }]]></string>
    <string name="Question16_2019_set1"><![CDATA[Consider the following C program \n #include<stdio.h> int jumble(int x, int y){ x=2*x+y; return x; } int main(){ int x=2, y=5; y=jumble(y,x); x=jumble(y,x); printf(“%d \n”, x); return 0; }]]></string>
    <string name="Question17_2019_set1"><![CDATA[Consider the following C program is executed on a Unix/Linux system : #include <unistd.h> int main() { int i; for (i=0; i<10; i++) if (i%2 == 0) fork(); return 0; }]]></string>
    <string name="Question18_2019_set1">Two numbers are chosen independently and uniformly at random from the set {1, 2,...,13}. The probability (rounded off to 3 decimal places) that their 4-bit (unsigned binary representations have the same most significant bit is ___________.</string>
    <string name="Qustion19_2019_set1">An array of 25 distinct elements is to be sorted using quicksort. Assume that the pivot element is chosen uniformly at random. The probability that the pivot element gets placed in the worst possible location in the first round of partitioning (rounded off to 2 decimal places) is________.</string>
    <string name="Question20_2019_set1">Which one of the following kinds of derivation is used by LR parsers?</string>
    <string name="Question21_2019_set1">Which one of the following statements is NOT correct about the B+ tree data structure used for creating an index of a relational database table?</string>
    <string name="Qustion23_2019_set1">Let X be a square matrix. Consider the following two statements on X. I. X is invertible. II. Determinant of X is non-zero. Which one of the following is TRUE?</string>
    <string name="Question24_2019_set1">Consider the following two statements about database transaction schedules: I. Strict two-phase locking protocol generates conflict serializable schedules that are also recoverable. II. Timestamp-ordering concurrency control protocol with Thomas’ Write Rule can generate view serializable schedules that are not conflict serializable. Which of the above statements is/are TRUE?</string>
    <string name="Question25_2019_set1">Which of the following protocol pairs can be used to send and retrieve e-mails (in that order)?</string>
</resources>